{"subjectID":1,"researchID":"SonificationResearch","dateTime":"2020-12-21T16:53:51.7359175+01:00","answers":[{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 1 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":14.9588728,"questionAnswerTime":14.9588718},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 2 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":15.6437826,"questionAnswerTime":15.6437826},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 3 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":16.3437824,"questionAnswerTime":16.3437824},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 4 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":17.0608139,"questionAnswerTime":17.060812},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 5 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":18.7439632,"questionAnswerTime":18.7439632},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"What is the mimimal noticable diffrence for this participant?","answer":"9.895552","questionAskTime":25.53752,"questionAnswerTime":25.53752},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":25.5477734,"questionAnswerTime":27.558588},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"10.63931","questionAskTime":27.5650425,"questionAnswerTime":29.4589462},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"9.208753","questionAskTime":29.4606552,"questionAnswerTime":30.2249413},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"11.17491","questionAskTime":30.2266941,"questionAnswerTime":31.7087574},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"8.084453","questionAskTime":31.7104626,"questionAnswerTime":32.7229},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"9.010032","questionAskTime":32.72477,"questionAnswerTime":33.751667},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"10.7151","questionAskTime":33.7533722,"questionAnswerTime":34.6166229},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"9.705247","questionAskTime":34.6183243,"questionAnswerTime":37.14974},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":25.5477734,"questionAnswerTime":27.558588},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":37.1500053,"questionAnswerTime":40.9406776},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":25.5477734,"questionAnswerTime":27.558588},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":37.1500053,"questionAnswerTime":40.9406776},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":40.95231,"questionAnswerTime":43.6987724},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"4.850084","questionAskTime":43.7062836,"questionAnswerTime":44.3652},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"10.7719","questionAskTime":44.3669052,"questionAnswerTime":45.04019},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"7.941415","questionAskTime":45.04197,"questionAnswerTime":46.4134521},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"8.512363","questionAskTime":46.4152374,"questionAnswerTime":48.25657},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"10.1429","questionAskTime":48.2582932,"questionAnswerTime":50.1545677},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"4.887798","questionAskTime":50.1563454,"questionAnswerTime":52.33952},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"10.98882","questionAskTime":52.3412628,"questionAnswerTime":53.1309967},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":25.5477734,"questionAnswerTime":27.558588},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":37.1500053,"questionAnswerTime":40.9406776},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":40.95231,"questionAnswerTime":43.6987724},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":53.13124,"questionAnswerTime":56.8891},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":25.5477734,"questionAnswerTime":27.558588},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":37.1500053,"questionAnswerTime":40.9406776},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":40.95231,"questionAnswerTime":43.6987724},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":53.13124,"questionAnswerTime":56.8891},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 3 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":56.90109,"questionAnswerTime":59.105423},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"11.5366","questionAskTime":59.1128578,"questionAnswerTime":61.755},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"5.720716","questionAskTime":61.75673,"questionAnswerTime":63.946846},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"6.001007","questionAskTime":63.94858,"questionAnswerTime":65.7047958},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"11.07315","questionAskTime":65.7065353,"questionAnswerTime":68.2711945},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"4.528935","questionAskTime":68.272934,"questionAnswerTime":69.02952},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"10.50128","questionAskTime":69.03123,"questionAnswerTime":70.38572},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"10.01294","questionAskTime":70.38747,"questionAnswerTime":71.80411},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.590366,"questionAnswerTime":11.7273817},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":11.7520523,"questionAnswerTime":13.6326332},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":20.75059,"questionAnswerTime":25.52586},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":25.5477734,"questionAnswerTime":27.558588},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":37.1500053,"questionAnswerTime":40.9406776},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":40.95231,"questionAnswerTime":43.6987724},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":53.13124,"questionAnswerTime":56.8891},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 3 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":56.90109,"questionAnswerTime":59.105423},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 3?","answer":"3","questionAskTime":71.80441,"questionAnswerTime":74.60345}]}